android-sale.com 2012-10-03

# Privacy Policy

## What personal information do we collect?

As set forth in more details below, Android-Sale.com ("Android-Sale" or "We") collects personal information that you provide when using the Android-Sale website ("Site"). This information includes your first and last name, email address and a password when you create Your Android-Sale account. You can browse this Site without creating an account, but you will need to create an account when you purchase something and in order to take advantage of certain features, such as "Save for Later," "Address Book" and the other Android-Sale services. We may ask you to confirm your personal information when you contact our Customer Service department. This will allow us to protect your confidentiality by verifying your identity.

Android-Sale does not intentionally collect personal information about children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 18 but at least 13 years of age you may use this Site only under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian who agrees to be bound by the Android-Sale's Terms of Use. Children under the age of 13 may not use this Site and parents or legal guardians may not agree to the Android-Sale Terms of Use on their behalf. If you do not agree to (or cannot comply with) any of the Android-Sale's Terms of Use, do not use this Site.

## Purchase Information

When you make a purchase from Android-Sale, we collect your name and payment method information. We collect this information in order to bill you for your purchase. We also collect information that allows us to ship your order. This includes the name, billing address, shipping address, and phone number of the intended recipient(s).

When you create an account at Android-Sale, you can choose to save your billing information in "My Android-Sale." You can also save one or more shipping addresses in Your Android-Sale Address Book. You may change or delete this saved information anytime. Simply go to My Android-Sale. Log in with your ID and password, then edit or delete whatever personal information you wish.

## Services Account Information

We collect personal information from users who wish to use any of the Android-Sale services. In order to use these services you must provide your email address and password or create an account at Android-Sale.

## Cookies and Other Computer Information

When you visit Android-Sale, you will be assigned a permanent "cookie" (a small text file) to be stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of the cookie is to identify you when you visit this Site so we can enhance and customize your online purchase experience.

You can choose to browse on Android-Sale without cookies, but without these identifier files you will not be able to complete a purchase or take advantage of certain features of this Site. These features include storing your shopping cart for later use and, in the future, providing a more personalized shopping experience. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. We also collect certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page during a visit to Android-Sale. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, browser type and the address of a referring web site, if any. We collect this information to enhance the quality of your experience during your visit to this Site and will not sell or rent this information to any third parties. We also contract with third parties to provide us with data collection and reporting services regarding our customers' activities on this Site and to track and measure performance of our marketing efforts. These third parties may use cookies and may receive anonymous information about your browsing and buying activity on this Site. None of your personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, email address, etc.) will be received by or shared with these third parties.

## Other times we may collect personal information

From time to time, Android-Sale may conduct surveys and contests via this Site, email, other media. If you choose to participate, we may request your name, email address, mailing address and other personal information. We will never sell or rent such information to any third parties.

## How we use your personal information?

Information we collect on Android-Sale may be used to enhance your shopping experience in the following ways:

  * Deliver merchandise and services that you purchase online.
  * Register you as a member of Android-Sale.
  * Prevent fraud and bill you for your purchases.
  * Confirm your orders.
  * Respond to your customer-service inquiries or requests.
  * Communicate great values and featured items to you.
  * Find and stock the products you want.
  * Customize your purchase experience

## How is your information protected?

We use the latest in encryption technology, including 128 bit SSL encryption to ensure that any sensitive information that is sent by you to us via the Internet is protected from unauthorized interception. We employ the latest in firewall protection to prevent unauthorized access into our information storage areas. We maintain a rigorous hiring process to screen out potential employees with criminal backgrounds. All employees that we do hire have to sign a confidentiality agreement that forbids them from disclosing any information to which the employee has access, to other individuals or entities. We also have back up servers and power supplies to guard against power outages and other natural occurrences that could pose a threat to the integrity of your personal information. Passwords are required in order for you to gain access to your account. Once an account has been terminated, measures are taken to remove those users from the system who no longer need access to our system.

When an employee is terminated or is no longer with the company, we change the access codes that the employee used to access any customer accounts. Account login sessions are terminated after three failed login attempts; all terminated login sessions are logged for follow-up. Passwords must contain at least six characters, one of which is nonalphanumeric. Unused customer accounts, those that have shown no activity for 6 months are purged from our system

## When and with whom can we share your personal information?

We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We will share personal customer information only with our agents, representatives, service providers, and contractors for limited purposes, including fulfilling customer orders; offering certain products and services in connection with this Site; communicating to customers; providing customer service; storing, sharing and retrieving customers' photo images in our Photo Center; enhancing and improving clients' purchase experience; enabling access to our partners' web sites; providing a personalized purchase experience; preventing fraud and completing payment method processing. Aside from the purposes described above, we will never share your personal information with any other third parties unless we have your express permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the disclosure is required to prevent harm or injury (such as product recalls, fraud, claims or other liability) or to comply with valid legal processes (subpoenas, warrants) or as required by law. We may share aggregated demographic and statistical information with our partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

## How can you control the use of your personal information?

You can modify or delete your personal information anytime. Simply go to My Android-Sale. Log in with your ID and password, then edit or delete whatever personal information you wish. Do not share Your Android-Sale password with anyone. Other than on this Site, Android-Sale will never ask you for your password.

## More about your privacy

We realize that making purchases at Android-Sale, or any other web site, requires trust on your part. We value your trust very highly, and pledge to you, our clients that we will work to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us and that your personal information will only be used as set forth in this Policy. This includes your name, address, phone number, email address or checking account information, in addition to any other personal information that can be linked to you, personally. We believe that you have a right to know, before purchase at Android-Sale or at any other time, exactly what information we might collect from you, why we collect it and how we use it.

We do not and will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone. You have the right to control your personal information as you see fit.

If you have an account at Android-Sale and you want to change, modify or delete any of your personal information, you can do so anytime by going to My Android-Sale. Log in with your ID and password, then edit or delete whatever personal information you wish.

Android-Sale may provide links to certain third party web sites. This Privacy Policy applies only to activities conducted and personal information collected on this Android-Sale web site. Other web sites may have their own policies regarding privacy and security.

Android-Sale will obtain your consent before allowing the download of any software from the Android-Sale Site, and Android-Sale will not automatically download any software to your computer system. Once you consent to the initial download of any software, you may receive automatic updates or patches pertaining to such software. You understand and agree that any material, including but not limited to downloaded software, required or automated updates, modifications, reinstallations, or software otherwise obtained through the use of the Android-Sale web Site is done at your own discretion and risk and that you will be solely responsible for any damages to your computer system or loss of data that may result from any such material

## Updates to this policy

If we change or update this Privacy Notice, we will post changes and updates on this Site so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, use, and disclose. We encourage you to review this Privacy Notice from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Notice has been changed or updated.
